Be courageous. Report it. Life gets better.
An Open Secret is a documentary, crime film directed by Amy J. Berg.
An investigation into accusations of teenagers being
sexually abused within the film industry.
Self, played by Evan Henzi.
Self, played by Michael Egan III.
Self - Actor, Diff'rent Strokes, played by Todd Bridges.
Self, played by Joey Coleman.
Self, played by Nicholas Stojanovich.
Self - Child Talent Manager, played by Michael Harrah.
An Open Secret is a 2014 American documentary film directed by Amy J.
Berg exposing child sexual abuse in the film industry in California.
The film explores themes of pedophilia, child abuse,
rape, sexual abuse, movie business.